

### **SKILLS**

- Basic SQL
- Basic HTML, CSS, JS
- Basic C#
- Basic Python
- Excel proficiency
- Word proficiency
- Driving license category B
- Machine maintenance
- Team oversight
- Hand and power tools
- Job order prioritisation
- Detail Orientated
- Mechanical knowledge
- Organisation
- Metalworking abilities
- Technical drawing interpretation
- Unified Modelling Language (UML) methodology
- Electrical qualifications up to 1kV

#### **EDUCATION**

College of Economics and Computer Science WSEI | Krakow

Applied Computer Science: Applied Computer Science

Zespół Szkół Mechanicznych Nr 1 | Krakow Automotive Technician: Automotive Technician

### **CERTIFICATIONS**

# Damian Cebula

- 07926624783
- damiancebula.dc1@gmail.com
- 66 Egerton Road, Prescot, Merseyside L34 3LT

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

A trustworthy employee with many years of experience in various fields of work, always fulfilling the tasks assigned to him, eager to develop and hone new skills without neglecting his duties. Can boast of reliability and high resilience to stress associated with performing multiple duties at once. Excellently adept at learning new solutions while working in a team and supervising tasks. A methodical worker who completes practical tasks in line with a tight schedule, approaching problems with a First Time Fix (FTF) mindset and documenting work accurately. Facilitates productive workflow through effective collaboration and meticulous planning.

# **WORK HISTORY**

09/2024 - Current

Dryliner

**GEORGEE LIMITED** | United Kngdom

- Improved safety standards by following industry regulations closely during all drylining tasks.
- Delivered high-quality finishes for increased customer satisfaction with a keen eye to detail.
- Ensured smooth operations whilst maintaining tools and equipment.
- Installed plasterboard partitions to create designated spaces in commercial buildings.
- Cut and fitted plasterboard panels to size, using hand tools and power tools with precision.
- Sustained safety protocols by ensuring proper and safe usage of equipment and materials.
- Measured and marked surfaces for fixing drywall panels in residential and commercial buildings.
- Utilised laser levels and straightedges to ensure alignment and level of wall and ceiling structures.
- Installed metal stud partitions, ceilings, and raised flooring systems to meet client specifications.

09/2021 - Current

**Fitter** 

PRU MEGA-REM Sp. z o. o | Kraków, Poland

• Maintenance of cranes, hoists, and winches.

- Information Technology
   Specialist Databases,
   Certiport, score 936/1000
   (Certified)
- Information Technology
   Specialist Software
   Development, Certiport,
   score 869/1000 (Certified)
- AZ-900: Microsoft Azure Fundamentals, Certiport, score 940/1000 (Microsoft Certified)
- Information Technology Specialist HTML and CSS, Certiport, score 824/1000(Certified)
- Information Technology Spercialist Networking, Certiport, score 900/1000(Certified)

## **LANGUAGES**

**English, Polish** Native language

**English** 

Upper intermediate (B2)

Polish

Proficient (C2)

- Operation of freight and passenger elevators, forklifts, and Annealing processes for welds.
- Holding SEP (Electrical qualifications up to 1kV.), Slinger, and Annealing Process Operation certifications.
- Preparation of measurement and post-construction documentation.
- Organization and management of people and heavy equipment at the workplace.
- Excel database management.
- Supervising the work of a crew.
- Power plant Engineer

11/2020 - 12/2020

Prefabricated House Assembler
Smart Bau & Montage Gmbh | Niemcy, Germany

- Preparation and securing of walls for vertical transport.
- Communication with the crane operator and handling of lifted elements.
- Preparation of the base and setting of house elements as well as securing.
- Reading plans.
- Laying roof tiles.
- Driving a bus-type vehicle up to 3.5 tons, transporting people, tools, and materials.
- Sealing the building. Installation of OSB and drywall boards.
- Collaborated with line group to divide tasks and assemble products before target deadlines.
- Used clamps and to position and hold work pieces in preparation of assembly.
- Studied parts to identify and segregate defects, recording findings.
- Kept workstation tidy to comply with health and safety and cleanliness standards.

04/2018 - 10/2020

Dryliner

GEORGEE LIMITED | United Kingdom, Wielka Brytania

- Cut and fitted plasterboard panels to size, using hand tools and power tools with precision.
- Sustained safety protocols by ensuring proper and safe usage of equipment and materials.
- Measured and marked surfaces for fixing drywall panels in residential and commercial buildings.
- Utilised laser levels and straightedges to ensure alignment and level of wall and ceiling structures.
- Installed metal stud partitions, ceilings, and raised flooring systems to meet client specifications.

10/2015 - 04/2018

Warehouse Worker/Forklift Operator Poppies LTD | United Kingdom

• Order picking, arranging goods on a pallet and securing them with wrap.

- Completing documents for the carrier and checking the accuracy of orders.
- Operating a high-reach electric forklift.
- Transported pallets and heavy stock using forklift equipment.
- Picked orders to meet productivity targets.
- Understood warehouse product placement, enabling efficient picking and packing services.
- Cleaned and maintained warehouse in compliance with safety standards.

# **HOBBIES AND INTEREST**

- Paintball
- Strategy gamesSports
- My hobby is taking on challenges in creating new solutions.
- Traveling.
- Gaining knowledge and continuous development.